Guide to the Boy Scouts of America Collection of ephemeral material, 1838-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series XVII: Oversize Newspapers
  - The Washington Times (Washington, D.C.). (Oversize 11)
    - 1985National Scout Jamboree Souvenir Edition
    - Map and legend for the 1985 National Scout Jamboree
    - 1989National Scout Jamboree Souvenir Edition
  - Red River Valley Council Scout News n.d. (Oversize 11)
- Series XVIII: Oversize Newspaper and Magazine Clippings
  - The Montclair Times (Oversize 11)
    - Scout Merit Badge Show advertisement 1/23/40
  - Los Angeles Examiner (Los Angeles, CA) 7/17-18 & 20-24/53 (Oversize 11)
    Third National Boy Scout Jamboree. Irvine Ranch, CA
  - BSA National Public Relations Service 1954 (Oversize 11)
    Various syndicated articles incorporated into one newspaper
  - Boy's LifeMagazine 7/64 (Oversize 11)
    Sixth National Boy Scout Jamboree. Valley Forge, PA 7/64
  - The Cincinnati Enquirer (Cincinnati, OH) 7/64 (Oversize 11)
    Sixth National Boy Scout Jamboree. Valley Forge, PA 7/20/64
  - Journal and Sentinel 7/19/64 (Oversize 11)
    Sixth National Boy Scout Jamboree. Valley Forge, PA 7/19/64
  - The Philadelphia Inquirer 7/17/1964 (Oversize 11)
    Sixth National Boy Scout Jamboree. Valley. Forge, PA 7/17/64
  - "Hero of Mafeking". The Sunday Telegraph 9/18 & 25/66 (Oversize 11)
  - "Den Mother" n.d. (Oversize 11)
  - "Life on the American Newsfront: 26,000 Boy Scouts Hold a Jamboree" (First National Scout Jamboree. Washington, D.C.) n.d. (Oversize 11)